<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Butbka World</title>
    <link>http://example.org/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Butbka World</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>ru-ru</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2024 10:06:10 +0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://example.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Multitracks Scraper Go</title>
      <link>http://example.org/projects/multitracks-scraper-go/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Jan 2024 10:06:10 +0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/projects/multitracks-scraper-go/</guid>
      <description>multitracks-scraper-go Link to heading Multitracks Scraper CLI Tool for Reaper DAW Projects
Overview Link to heading multitracks-scraper-go is a command-line interface (CLI) tool written in Go that enables users to scrape web pages for song information and automatically create new projects for the Reaper DAW. This tool simplifies the process of setting up projects, making it more efficient for music producers and engineers(Me mostly :) ).
Features Link to heading Web Scraping: Retrieve song information from web page.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>http://example.org/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 16:23:11 +0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/about/</guid>
      <description>Hello there! 👋 I&amp;rsquo;m Viktar, programming enthusiast currently living in Georgia. Here&amp;rsquo;s a bit about me:
I have a passion for programming and have had the pleasure of working with various languages over the years. Here are some languages I&amp;rsquo;ve explored:
JavaScript Lua Python Golang Apart from coding, I have a few other interests:
Music: I love both listening to and playing music. It&amp;rsquo;s a great way for me to relax and unwind.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Brial bot</title>
      <link>http://example.org/projects/brial_bot/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 16:06:02 +0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/projects/brial_bot/</guid>
      <description>Meet Brial Bot, the Telegram chatbot designed to turn your messages into captivating Brial code! Brial Bot adds a dash of mystery and entertainment to your conversations with its unique text conversion feature.
Features: Link to heading Brial Code Conversion: Simply send your text messages to Brial Bot, and experience the excitement as it transforms your words into intriguing Brial code. Elevate your chat experience with a touch of cryptic fun!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kilogram</title>
      <link>http://example.org/projects/kilogram/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Jan 2024 10:30:35 +0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/projects/kilogram/</guid>
      <description>Kilogram - CLI Telegram Client Link to heading Kilogram is a command-line interface (CLI) Telegram client designed for integration with other CLI tools and automation purposes. While currently in a &amp;ldquo;scratch&amp;rdquo; state, it already offers some functionality for you to explore.
Features Link to heading Chat Management: Fetch a list of your chats or view the chat history for a specific conversation.
Contact Retrieval: Fetch your contacts with ease.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
